export const lvl1 = [
  {
    id: 1,
    question: `In what year was Brisbane founded?`,
    answers: ['1824', '1834', '1844'],
    correctAnswer: '1824',
  },
  {
    id: 2,
    question: `What significant event took place in Brisbane in 1988?`,
    answers: ['Summer Olympics', 'World Expo', '150th anniversary of the city'],
    correctAnswer: 'World Expo',
  },
  {
    id: 3,
    question: `What was Brisbane called before it received its official name?`,
    answers: ['Edmonton', 'Brisbane River', 'Moreton Bay Penal Settlement'],
    correctAnswer: 'Moreton Bay Penal Settlement',
  },
  {
    id: 4,
    question: `What factor contributed to Brisbane's growth in the 19th century?`,
    answers: ['Gold rush', 'Industrial revolution', 'Opening of the railway'],
    correctAnswer: 'Gold rush',
  },
  {
    id: 5,
    question: `When did Brisbane become the capital of Queensland?`,
    answers: ['1859', '1869', '1879'],
    correctAnswer: '1859',
  },
  {
    id: 6,
    question: `Who is considered the founder of Brisbane?`,
    answers: [
      'Captain James Cook',
      'Lieutenant William Brisbane',
      'General John Blake',
    ],
    correctAnswer: 'Lieutenant William Brisbane',
  },
  {
    id: 7,
    question: `In what year was Brisbane declared a city?`,
    answers: ['1900', '1925', '1859'],
    correctAnswer: '1859',
  },
  {
    id: 8,
    question: `What was the name of the first hospital in Brisbane?`,
    answers: [
      'Brisbane Hospital',
      "St. Luke's Hospital",
      'Queensland State Hospital',
    ],
    correctAnswer: "St. Luke's Hospital",
  },
  {
    id: 9,
    question: `What natural disaster affected Brisbane in 2011?`,
    answers: ['Earthquake', 'Flood', 'Hurricane'],
    correctAnswer: 'Flood',
  },
  {
    id: 10,
    question: `What monument was unveiled in Brisbane to commemorate the city's 150th anniversary?`,
    answers: [
      'Australian Soldiers Memorial',
      'Founders of Brisbane Monument',
      'Queen Victoria Monument',
    ],
    correctAnswer: 'Founders of Brisbane Monument',
  },
];
